Hey Jonathan, thanks for taking the time
for us today. We're gonna start with
Olivia and then go to Rube.
>> Hey Jonathan, how are you? Um, welcome
to Philly. It's nice to meet you. First
of all, um,
>> how did why Philly? Um, and yeah, just
kind of what what led to this decision
for you to come here?
>> Hey, how you doing? Um I I kind of
admired um what this team's been
building over the last few years and
just kind of um some of the dominance
they've been performing, you know,
across the league and year in year out.
Um they're one of the teams that's in a
discussion. Um and so to be a part of
something like that is kind of my
calling card.
>> We'll go to Rube and then Zach.
>> All right, we'll jump to Zach and then
go to Martin Frank. Hey Jonathan,
congratulations. What kind of role do
you anticipate here? And um do you view
yourself, you know, being able to play
multiple positions or is it just
primarily corner?
>> Yeah, I mean that's kind of been my role
uh in my career is just to be available,
you know, be be a football player. I
just enjoy playing football. Um try to
get in, learn the defense, and be
available, you know, whatever position
they need me to play. Uh it's kind of
been what I've done, you know, my entire
career.
>> We'll go to Martin and then Dave.
>> Hi, Jonathan. Um, I want to ask you like
what your impressions are. Um, I don't
know if you've had a chance to look at
uh Quinan Mitchell or Cooper Deene over
the past year or two. Um, but if you
have, just what you think think about
them and and how you can help them
develop even more as teammates.
>> Yeah, I mean there's some really really
good young players um that have have
already established themselves in this
league uh made a lot of plays. Um, I
think I can try to come help in, give
them a different perspective, uh, with
some of the things I've seen over the
years. Um, and just try to be a, um,
just be of help, you know, to those guys
and try to help them build, you know, in
their careers because, you know, they
have, you know, promising futures.
>> We'll go to Dave and then John McMullen.
>> Hi, Jonathan. I know you have some
crossover with Mike Pelgrino. Uh, what
is he like as a coach and and what's
that connection like for you?
>> Yeah, Mike, I mean, we spent a lot of
time in New England. Um he is um very
very energetic, you know, hardworking.
Um just one of those guys that'll
that'll be in early and leave late as a
coach. Um he always tries to get guys as
prepared as they can. You know, that's
one thing that I admire about him is
just how hardworking he is as a coach uh
to make sure the guys have everything
that they need.
>> We'll go to John McMullen and then to
Rube.
>> Uh hey, welcome to Philly first of all.
And uh you know, I I noticed in your
career early on it was a lot of slot.
you made the transition outside about
four years ago. What what kind of was
behind that transition? What what made
you the kind of player who can do that?
And and are you more comfortable with
one or the other?
>> Yeah, I think it was more so of of team
need. You know, I played uh slot early
in my career. Uh played safety in the in
the Rams Super Bowl and then, you know,
we needed a perimeter corner that year.
Um, and I think, you know, coach had
saw, you know, how I'd practiced and,
you know, how I'd been playing and he
felt very comfortable, you know, playing
me outside and I kind of, you know, end
up just being out there for the last few
years of my career. Uh, but I think, um,
just building the consistency, building
the trust of, you know, teammates,
coaches is what you always strive for.
And so, um, I just try to give coaches
the the best, um, the best options with
me. Just try to be the best player in
all positions so they feel comfortable,
put me anywhere.
>> We'll go to Rube and then back to
Olivia.
Hey Jonathan, welcome to Philly. You you
mentioned your uh your impressions of
the Eagles as an outsider, I guess, over
over a period of years. Specifically
last year, I guess being in a division.
What specifically did you see about the
organization that appealed to you?
>> Yeah, I mean, just just winning, you
know, and you you watch week in and week
out, you know, finding ways to win. Uh I
mean, like every program, dealing with
adversity, but just um just finding ways
to win and still stay relevant. I think
that's so hard in this league. You know,
have great players, you know, every team
has good players, but just finding that
chemistry in a team to still be
relevant, make the playoffs. Um, I think
I think that's special year in and year
out because, you know, a lot of teams
will be in the playoffs one year, um,
you know, go through some adversity, go
through offseason, and you might not
hear for them for three or four more,
you know, years and to be back in the
playoffs. And so, um, just a tradition
this team has, you could see that, um,
week in and week out.
>> We'll go to Olivia and then Martin.
Hi again. Um, what what keeps you going
going into year 11?
>> Yeah, I mean always football. I love it.
You know, I just I love the game of
football. Um, I was joking with my wife.
I was like, you know, if Sundays, you
know, even when I'm done playing
football, if I can find a park to play
some football with, I'm I'm going to
continue to do it. It's just um I just
love I love the game of football. Always
have. Um I can't remember life before
football. Every fall since I was four,
I've been playing football. So, um, it's
just it's just what I know.
>> We'll go to Martin and then Zach.
>> Hey, Jonathan. Uh, I I understand you
have an interesting story about how you
got to Philly today or something. And
and also, if you could also, you played
against the Eagles in the Super Bowl
like eight or nine years ago. Um, well,
you didn't play actually, you were in
IR, but what was that experience like?
What do you remember from that game? It
was quite an offensive game, correct?
Yeah. Yeah. Uh I guess to start with
that, it was it was definitely a
phenomenal offensive game. Uh so as a
defensive player and and and being hurt
earlier in the playoffs, uh it just it
hurt to watch hurt to watch you guys uh
you know, win that. I was on a little
scooter and I can just remember just
green confetti just falling on my head
as as I'm trying to scoot across the
field and um you know, you guys you know
found a way to win that game and it was
just you know, one of those Super Bowls
where you know, both teams were back and
forth and you guys, you know, put on a
show. Um, and so the interesting story
of getting here, that's alluding, I
guess, to the aviation. Uh, found a
little passion for aviation a few years
back and, uh, flew up here today, uh,
for for signing. And so, it's something
something a little hobby of mine that I
enjoy doing.
>> We'll go to Zach and then Christian.
>> Hey, I was I was going to ask you about
becoming an undrafted free agent and
making 11 years, but uh, now that you
talked about your passion for aviation,
how did you get into that? Um, and and
like what if you look at today, where
did you fly from to get here?
>> Uh, yeah, it was just I'm always looking
for, you know, new hobbies and, you
know, I grew up as a country boy and so
always outside, you know, bikes,
four-wheelers, and just kind of kind of
was my niche and, uh, got exposed to
general aviation, took a Discovery
Flight and I fell in love with it. And
so, you know, hopped over from Charlotte
today over to here. And so, it was it
was a quick flight, but um, like I said,
anytime I can fly, I love it. And then
if if I can just ask you, you know, you
mentioned what keeps you going, but it's
rare for an undrafted player to last
this long in the in the NFL. What's been
your like a differencemaker? How have
have you been able to do it?
>> Yeah, I just try to stay grounded, stay
as low to the ground as I can and and
always feel like I'm trying to prove
myself. Um, you know, uh, I love to
compete and so I feel like as you get
older, I can remember being being the
younger guy in the room, you know, full
of veterans, you know, Deon McCordi and
those guys and just trying to compete
with them and and so now being, you
know, the older guy in the room, just
still, you know, having that joy of the
game, coming out competing in practice
and games and just, you know, still
having that childhood joy of of playing
football is definitely what keeps you
going.
>> We'll go to Christian and back to Rube.
>> Uh, hey, welcome to Philly. Um, can you
just talk about your game a little bit
and your your mindset as a player and
what fans can expect uh from you this
coming season?
>> Yeah, I I just I love aggression. You
know, I love to, you know, fly around on
the football field, make plays, um,
support my teammates, and just, you
know, um, just try to be cerebral player
and and try to, you know, dissect
offenses and and really understand, you
know, how they're trying to attack us
and just go out there, you know, and
compete. You know, I think I have a a
good philosophy of, you know, how how
defenses are good at, you know, stopping
offenses and, you know, eliminating
explosive plays. You know, as a
quarterback, you play long enough, you
realize you're not going to stop every
play. You start to learn which, you
know, which plays are the important
plays, um, that you have to make and
which become gamechanging plays.
>> We'll close out with Rube here, unless
we have any final questions.
>> One more general aviation question, I
guess. Uh, what kind of plane do you
fly? And uh did you land at at Philly
airport or a smaller airport?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I have a a TVM and so yeah,
I flew in to to Philly airport uh this
morning. It's kind of kind of nice to
have the little approach over, you know,
the Delaware River was kind was kind of
a nice nice touch for the morning.
>> All right, thanks Jonathan. We
appreciate your time today.
>> Thank you guys. that you have me.